Register of the Eric Voegelin papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence (Alphabetical File), 1928-1984
  - Deutsche Gesellschaft für Soziologie (5), 1959-1975 (Box-folder 10: 6)
  - Deutsche UNESCO-Kommission (Wolfgang Hug) (12), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 10: 7)
  - Deutsche Vereinigung für Politische Wissenschaft (25), 1958-1978 (Box-folder 10: 8)
  - Deutsche Zeitung (Friedrich Thalmann) (5), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 10: 9)
  - Dictionary of the History of Ideas, (4), 1968 (Box-folder 10: 10)
  - Dietze, Gottfried (50), 1959-1980 (Box-folder 10: 11)
  - Dietze, Horst E. (1), 1950 (Box-folder 10: 12)
  - Diez del Corral, Professor (1), 1959 (Box-folder 10: 13)
  - Doerrie, Heinrich (1), 1982 (Box-folder 10: 14)
  - Doherty, Joseph E. (6), 1972-1979 (Box-folder 10: 15)
  - Doolittle, Lawrence W. (7), 1972-1976 (Box-folder 10: 16)
  - Dorschel, Alfons (1), 1962 (Box-folder 10: 17)
  - DuBrul, Stephen M., Jr. (55), 1961-1981 (Box-folder 10: 18)
  - Duke University (Calvin B. Hoover) (2), 1938 (Box-folder 10: 19)
  - Duke University Press (8), 1974-1981 (Box-folder 10: 20)
    Includes contract
  - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing (1), 1945 (Box-folder 10: 21)
    Regarding getting in contact with Eric Voegelin's relatives in Vienna.
  - Dyer, Philip W. (2), 1969 (Box-folder 10: 22)
  - Earhart Foundation. See Relm Foundation
  - East, John (8), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 10: 23)
  - Eckstein, Walter (1), 1944 (Box-folder 10: 24)
  - Ediciones Rialp (3), 1962-1963 (Box-folder 10: 25)
  - Edinger, Lewis J. (3), 1964-1965 (Box-folder 10: 26)
  - Edwin Mellen Press (Herbert Richardson) (1), 1981 (Box-folder 10: 27)
  - Efron, Robert (1), 1969 (Box-folder 10: 28)
  - Eidelberg, Paul (4), 1973 (Box-folder 10: 29)
  - Eliade, Mircea (1), 1966 (Box-folder 11: 1)
  - Elliott, William Y. (Harvard University) (24), 1938-1961 (Box-folder 11: 2)
  - Elmenau, Johannes von (1), 1981 (Box-folder 11: 3)
  - Emerson, Rupert (2), 1940 (Box-folder 11: 4)
  - Emory, Kenneth (1), 1971 (Box-folder 11: 5)
  - Emory University (Joseph M. Conant; Jack T. Sanders; Judson C. Ward., Jr.; Charles T. Lester; David H. Hesla; Betty Attwood) (22), 1966-1968 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - Engel-Janosi, Friedrich and Carlette (1st wife) and Christiana (2nd wife)
    Includes correspondence with Siegfried Bloch, René Augay, Joseph D. Ostermann, Arthur E. Whittemore, and Kent Roberts Greenfield.
    - 1938-1945 (Box-folder 11: 7)
    - 1946-1952 (Box-folder 11: 8)
      Includes a letter from Wilfrid Parsons to Friedrich Engel-Janosi
    - 1953-1959 (Box-folder 11: 9)
    - 1960-1981 (Box-folder 11: 10)
  - Engel-Janosi, Madeleine (5), 1942-1960 (Box-folder 11: 11)
  - Engisch, Karl (2), 1960 (Box-folder 11: 12)
  - English, Raymond (6), 1962-1968 (Box-folder 11: 13)
  - Engnell, Ivan (1), 1955 (Box-folder 11: 14)
  - Ernst, Carl (8), 1973-1977 (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Ernst Klett Verlag. See Klett-Cota
  - Eschenburg, Theodor (9), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Esslinger, William (2), 1955 (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Ettinger, Karl E. (United States. Congress. House of Representatives. Special Committee to Investigate Tax Exempt Foundations) (10), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Eubank, Earle (University of Cincinnati) (9), 1938-1941 (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Evans, Dale R. (5), 1974-1979 (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Fallon, Timothy P. (1), 1984 (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Falter, Jürgen (2), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 12: 8)
    Includes form letter of Karl W. Deutsch
  - Farrar, Strauss & Co. (Noonday Press) (3), 1964 (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Fay, Sidney B. (Harvard University) (2), 1942-1946 (Box-folder 12: 10)
  - Feibleman, James K. (2), 1947 (Box-folder 12: 11)
  - Feldstein, Leonard C. (2), 1976 (Box-folder 12: 12)
  - Fersch, Emerson C. (3), 1979 (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - Fetscher, Iring (4), 1962-1965 (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - Ficek, Karel and Ann (2), 1939 (Box-folder 12: 15)
  - Fine, Arthur L. (2), 1954 (Box-folder 12: 16)
  - Finer, Herman (4), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 12: 17)
  - Finnis, John M. (4), 1969 (Box-folder 12: 18)
  - Fischer, Brigitte B. (7), 1952-1969 (Box-folder 12: 19)
  - Fischer, Eric (3), 1942-1944 (Box-folder 12: 20)
  - Fischer, Hugo (17), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 12: 21)
  - Fisher, Harold H. (2), 1944 (Box-folder 12: 22)
  - Flanagan, Thomas (3), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 12: 23)
  - Fleischer, George (4), 1940-1941 (Box-folder 12: 24)
  - Fliess, Peter J. and Helen (28), 1955-1976 (Box-folder 12: 25)
  - Ford Foundation (Shepard Stone) (38), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 12: 26)
    Includes memoranda and correspondence with Jürgen Gebhardt and Johannes von Elmenau regarding funding for the Geschwister-Scholl Institut für Politische Wissenschaft (Universität München)
  - Foreign Policy Association (Raymond S. Buell, Vera Micheles Dean) (5), 1937-1938 (Box-folder 12: 27)
  - Forschungsinstitut für Europäische Gegenwartskunde (Friedrich Hansen-Löve) (1), 1952 (Box-folder 12: 28)
  - Forschungsinstitut für Politische Wissenschaft und Europäische Fragen der Universität zu Köln (F. A. Hermens) (2), 1968 (Box-folder 12: 29)
  - Forschungskreis für Symbolik (Hans A. Fischer-Barnicol) (1), 1969 (Box-folder 12: 30)
  - Forsthoff, Ernest (3), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Foundation for Foreign Affairs (David S. Collier) (3), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Fraenkel, Ernst (5), 1962-1966 (Box-folder 13: 3)
    See also Freie Universität Berlin, Otto-Suhr-Institut
  - Francis, Emerich K. (11), 1958-1966 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Franke, Herbert (4), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Franz-Lieber-Haus (George W. Ineson) (3), 1960-1962 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Fraser, J. T. (2), 1976 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Freie Universität Berlin, Otto-Suhr-Institut (37), 1962-1971 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - Freund, Ludwig (2), 1956 (Box-folder 13: 9)
  - Freundeskreis der Liberalen Hochschulgruppen München (1), 1967 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - Fried, Hans (1), 1938 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Friedman, Milton (1), 1982 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - Friedmann, F. G. (4), 1963-1974 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Friedmann, Maximilian (1), 1943 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Friedmann, Walter and Lucy (4), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 13: 15)
  - Friedrich, Carl J. (41), 1938-1972 (Box-folder 13: 16)
  - Friedrich, Paul (2), 1977 (Box-folder 13: 17)
  - Friedrich, Walter (1), 1967 (Box-folder 13: 18)
  - Fries, Erich Julius (35), 1961-1981 (Box-folder 13: 19)
  - Fritz, Kurt and Louise von (4), 1963-1971 (Box-folder 13: 20)
  - Fritz Thyssen Stiftung (Ernst Coenen) (145), 1961-1967 (Box-folder 13: 21)
    Includes correspondence with Arno Baruzzi, Max Müller, Jürgen Gebhardt, Manfred Henningsen, Götz Briefs, Otto Brunner, Henry Deku, Arnold Bergsträsser; and reports regarding the Geschwister-Scholl-Institut für Politische Wissenschaft (Universität München)
  - Froehlich, Walter (12), 1938-1950 (Box-folder 13: 22)
  - Fulbright Commission (39), 1960-1967 (Box-folder 14: 1)
    Includes correspondence with, or regarding, Gregor Sebba, Winston L. King, Gerhart Niemeyer, Eric Waldman, Peter Odegard, George K. Romoser. See also Werner Levi, Hans H. Baerwald, and Carl Beck
  - Fuller, Timothy (1), 1981 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Furth, Josef Herbert (16), 1939-1981 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Gabriel, Leo (9), 1955-1968 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Gallagher, Jerry (1), undated (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Galmés de Fuentes, Alvaro (1), 1964 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Gangi, William (12), 1968-1981 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Garbarini, Michael (3), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14: 8)
    Includes correspondence with Robert Beum
  - Gargan, Edward T. (Loyola University) (8), 1958-1959 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - Gateway Editions. See Henry Regnery Company and University of Notre Dame Press
  - Gattenhof, Ilse (6), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Gebhardt, Jürgen (89), 1960-1983 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - George Washington University (W. Reed West) (2), 1938 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Germany (West). Auswärtiges Amt (2), 1961 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Germino, Dante
    - 1960-1975 (Box-folder 14: 14)
    - 1976-1984 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Geschichte und Gesellschaft (1), 1974 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Gesellschaft von Freunden und Förderern der Universität München. See Münchner Universitätsgesellschaft
  - Ghannam, Abdel Asis el- (7), 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15: 2)
    Includes correspondence with Peter von Sivers and G. F. Engholm
  - Giacometti, K. (3), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Gietl(?), Willi (2), 1980 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Gigon, Olof (1), 1950 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Giguere, Father (2), 1981 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Giuffrè Editore (Francesco Mercadante) (10), 1967-1971 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Glass, James M. (4), 1972 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Glatzer, Nahum N. (6), 1961-1972 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Going, Cathlene (1), 1980 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Golffing, Franz C. (3), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Goller, Karl (1), 1938 (Box-folder 15: 12)
  - Goscillo, M. (2), 1969 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Grace, Frank (University of Michigan) (5), 1952-1971 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Graham, George J., Jr. (4), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 15: 15)
  - Grazia, Sebastian de (2), 1953 (Box-folder 15: 16)
  - Green, William M. (1), 1959 (Box-folder 15: 17)
  - Greenbaum, Joseph J. (2), 1969 (Box-folder 15: 18)
  - Grenzmann, Wilhelm (1), 1961 (Box-folder 15: 19)
  - Gross, Hermann (2), 1967 (Box-folder 15: 20)
  - Gross, Leo (Institut International de Coopération Intellectuelle) (34), 1938-1980 (Box-folder 15: 21)
  - Grottian, Walter (13), 1959-1963 (Box-folder 15: 22)
  - Grundmann, Professor (2), 1960 (Box-folder 15: 23)
  - Guerreiro-Ramos, Alberto (5), 1973 (Box-folder 15: 24)
  - Guggenheim Foundation (Henry Allen Moe)
    See also Karl E. Ettinger, Aron Gurwitsch, Robert B. Heilman, and Alfred Schütz.
    - 1948-1957 (Box-folder 15: 25)
    - 1960-1970 (Box-folder 15: 26)
  - Gurian, Waldemar (42), 1938-1953 (Box-folder 15: 27)
    Includes a letter by Eric Voegelin on Hannah Arendt
  - Gurwitsch, Aron (55), 1947-1971 (Box-folder 15: 28)
  - Gutenbrunner, Siegfried (7), 1946-1949 (Box-folder 15: 29)
  - Gyorgy, Andrew (2), 1967-1971 (Box-folder 15: 30)
  - Haasch, Alan K. (1), 1967 (Box-folder 15: 31)
  - Häberle, Peter (1), 1981 (Box-folder 15: 32)
  - Haberler, Gottfried (47), 1938-1961 (Box-folder 15: 33)
  - Habermas, Jürgen (1), 1963 (Box-folder 15: 34)
  - Hacker, Paul (2), 1961 (Box-folder 15: 35)
  - Hagan, Charles B. (3), 1955-1957 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Hallett, Charles A. (2), 1976 (Box-folder 16: 2)
  - Hallowell, John H. (Duke University) (56), 1949-1975 (Box-folder 16: 3)
  - Haltom, John F. (2), 1959 (Box-folder 16: 4)
  - Hammitzsch, Horst (7), 1962-1967 (Box-folder 16: 5)
  - Hampe, Peter (24), 1969-1981 (Box-folder 16: 6)
    See also Harkness Fellowships
  - Hampel, Johannes (21), 1969-1981 (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Hamrell, Sven (2), 1949 (Box-folder 16: 8)
  - Hanak, Miroslav J. (2), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 16: 9)
  - Hand, C. H. See Yale University
  - Hankins, Frank Hamilton (2), 1938 (Box-folder 16: 10)
  - Hansen-Löve, Friedrich (3), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 16: 11)
  - Härdtl, Klara and Fritz (and children Gritti and Günter) (98), 1938-1976 (Box-folder 16: 12)
    Sister of Eric Voegelin. See also BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, Subject file, United States, Departure for, 1938
  - Hardy, John E. (3), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 16: 13)
  - Harkness Fellowships (Robert L. Johnston) (17), 1967-1971 (Box-folder 16: 14)
  - Harris, Robert J., Jr. (Louisiana State University) (85), 1942-1975 (Box-folder 16: 15)
    Includes correspondence with, and about, James A. Norton
  - Hartshorne, E. Y. (3), 1940 (Box-folder 16: 16)
  - Harvard University (Arthur N. Holcombe) (5), 1938-1964 (Box-folder 16: 17)
  - Harvard University Library (Richard de Gennaro) (5), 1965 (Box-folder 16: 18)
  - Harwick, B. Terence (3), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 16: 19)
  - Hasemann, R. J. (3), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 16: 20)
  - Hatton, Augustus R. (2), 1943 (Box-folder 16: 21)
  - Hausel, Clara (8), 1946-1954 (Box-folder 16: 22)
  - Havard, William C.
    - 1947-1962 (Box-folder 16: 23)
    - 1963-1980 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Hay, Stephen (3), 1975 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von (24), 1938-1966 (Box-folder 17: 3)
  - Hays, Sam S. (4), 1957-1976 (Box-folder 17: 4)
  - Heberle, Rudolf and Franziska (14), 1940-1981 (Box-folder 17: 5)
  - Hechos e ideas, Buenos Aires (2), 1951 (Box-folder 17: 6)
  - Heer, Friedrich (4), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Hegner, Jakob (3), 1950-1957 (Box-folder 17: 8)
  - Heilman, Robert B. (111), 1944-1981 (Box-folder 17: 9)
  - Heinen, Edmund (3), 1961-1966 (Box-folder 17: 10)
  - Hellmann, Manfred (2), 1966 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Helwig, G. (2), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 17: 12)
  - Henningsen, Bernd (7), 1969-1981 (Box-folder 17: 13)
  - Henningsen, Manfred
    - 1962-1968 (Box-folder 17: 14)
    - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17: 15)
    - 1971-1984 (Box-folder 17: 16)
  - Hennis, Wilhelm (36), 1958-1981 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Henry Regnery Company (76), 1962-1977 (Box-folder 18: 2)
  - Hentze, Carl Philip (3), 1968 (Box-folder 18: 3)
  - Hereth, Michael (15), 1969-1979 (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Heritage Foundation (2), 1978 (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Herlihy, Helen (2), 1940 (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - Herring, Helen B. (1), 1938 (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - Herrmann, Klaus J. (Sir George Williams University) (7), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Herwig, Dagmar (8), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 18: 9)
    Includes notes of Eric Voegelin. See also Hedda Herwig
  - Herwig, Hedda (16), 1968-1981 (Box-folder 18: 10)
    See also OFFICE FILES, Correspondence, 1968-1972
  - Herzfeld, Hans (1), 1973 (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Heuser, Wilhelm (3), 1974 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Hexner, Ervin (21), 1939-1958 (Box-folder 18: 13)
  - Heydte, F. A. v. d. (11), 1960-1963 (Box-folder 18: 14)
  - Hinderer, Walter (7), 1970-1975 (Box-folder 18: 15)
  - Hochland, (14), 1954-1963 (Box-folder 18: 16)
  - Hochschule für Politische Wissenschaften, Munich, West Germany (Helmut Kuhn) (4), 1961-1963 (Box-folder 18: 17)
  - Hochschulverband (Verbandsgruppe Universität München) (10), 1958-1976 (Box-folder 18: 18)
    Includes correspondence with Friedrich Lütge
  - Hocke, Gustav René (3), 1971 (Box-folder 18: 19)
  - Hoeppner, Jo Ann (7), 1965-1966 (Box-folder 18: 20)
  - Hoffmann, Rainer (10), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 18: 21)
  - Hoffmann, Walther (2), 1949 (Box-folder 18: 22)
  - Holcomb, Harmon R. (2), 1963 (Box-folder 18: 23)
  - Hollweck, Thomas (15), 1969-1978 (Box-folder 18: 24)
  - Holt, Robert T. (1), 1959 (Box-folder 18: 25)
    Includes correspondence with Mulford Q. Sibley
  - Holzheuer, Walter (1), 1970 (Box-folder 18: 26)
  - Hommes, Jakob (1), 1959 (Box-folder 18: 27)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace (W. Glenn Campbell) (90), 1961-1984 (Box-folder 18: 28)
    Includes correspondence with Richard V. Allen, Paul J. Friedrich, Alan H. Belmont, Lawson A. Pendleton, Richard F. Staar
  - Horkheimer, Max (4), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 18: 29)
  - Horner, Franz (5), 1969-1978 (Box-folder 18: 30)
  - Horst, Guido (2), 1980 (Box-folder 18: 31)
  - Horvath, Tibor (4), 1976 (Box-folder 18: 32)
  - Hsueh, S. S. (2), 1966 (Box-folder 18: 33)
  - Huber, Wilfried (4), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18: 34)
  - Hula, Eric (18), 1939-1952 (Box-folder 18: 35)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (5), 1939-1942 (Box-folder 18: 36)
  - Hutchinson Publishing Group (6), 1961-1964 (Box-folder 18: 37)
  - Hyneman, Charles S. (United States. War Department. Office of the Provost Marshal General) (2), 1943 (Box-folder 18: 38)
  - Institut de Science Economique Appliquée, Paris (2), 1949 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Institut für Friedensforschung, Universität zu Wien (Leo Gabriel, Heinrich Schneider, Rudolf Weiler) (37), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19: 2)
  - Institute for Christian Studies (1), 1983 (Box-folder 19: 3)
  - Institute for Cross-Cultural and Social-Scientific Research (Hans A. Fischer-Barnicol) (71), 1973-1984 (Box-folder 19: 4)
    Includes correspondence with Joseph E. Doherty, John C. Jacobs, and Wolfgang F. Somary.
  - Institute for Vico Studies (1), 1977 (Box-folder 19: 5)
  - Institute of Far Eastern Studies, University of Michigan (Robert B. Hall) (1), 1938 (Box-folder 19: 6)
  - Institute of International Education (Stephen P. Duggan) (3), 1938 (Box-folder 19: 7)
  - Intercollegiate Review, (17), 1966-1971 (Box-folder 19: 8)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute (5), 1968-1983 (Box-folder 19: 9)
  - Inter-Faith Council, University of North Carolina (James L. Haney) (1), 1954 (Box-folder 19: 10)
  - International Pioneer Academy (3), 1972 (Box-folder 19: 11)
  - International Platform Association (2), 1965 (Box-folder 19: 12)
  - International Political Science Association (3), 1958 (Box-folder 19: 13)
  - International Society for the Study of Time
    Includes correspondence with J. T. Fraser, G. J. Whitrow, J. H. Müller, and Jacques Merleau-Ponty.
    - 1966 (Box-folder 19: 14)
    - 1972-1974 (Box-folder 19: 15)
    - 1975-1978 (Box-folder 19: 16)
  - Internationale Robert-Musil Gesellschaft (Karl-Heinz Danner) (12), 1970-1974 (Box-folder 19: 17)
  - Ipsen, Günther (3), 1950 (Box-folder 19: 18)
  - Istituto Accademico di Roma (Richard Webster) (34), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 19: 19)
    Includes correspondence with Augusto DelNoce, Vincenzo Cappelletti, Elémire Zolla
  - Ivanka, Endre von (1), 1974 (Box-folder 19: 20)
  - Iverson, Lalla (1), 1979 (Box-folder 19: 21)
  - Ives, C. P. (2), 1967 (Box-folder 19: 22)
  - J.C.B. Mohr (Paul Siebeck) (19), 1927-1977 (Box-folder 20: 1)
    Includes contracts
  - Jacobs, John C. (12), 1969-1979 (Box-folder 20: 2)
  - Jacobson, Norman (1), 1964 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Jaeger, George W. (2), 1955 (Box-folder 20: 4)
  - Jaeger, Werner (2), 1949-1958 (Box-folder 20: 5)
  - Jaffa, Harry V. (1), 1974 (Box-folder 20: 6)
  - Jaffé, Georg
    - 1945-1958 (Box-folder 20: 7)
      See also Hans H. Baerwald
    - 1959-1965 (Box-folder 20: 8)
  - Jaffé, Hans (1), 1955 (Box-folder 20: 9)
  - Jecht, Horst (5), 1959-1964 (Box-folder 20: 10)
  - Johns Hopkins University (1), 1938 (Box-folder 20: 11)
    See also Fritz Machlup
  - Jonas, Hans (5), 1953-1963 (Box-folder 20: 12)
  - Jones, Hardin B. (4), 1968 (Box-folder 20: 13)
  - Journal of Politics (Paul L. Hanna) (1), 1945 (Box-folder 20: 14)
  - Journal of Social and Biological Structures (Harvey Wheeler) (2), 1983 (Box-folder 20: 15)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de (3), 1954 (Box-folder 20: 16)
  - Jungwirth, Georg (14), 1950-1974 (Box-folder 20: 17)
    Includes correspondence with the International Rescue Committee
  - Jungwirth, Kurt (2), 1970 (Box-folder 20: 18)
  - Jungwirth, Wolfgang (9), 1952-1957 (Box-folder 20: 19)
  - Junker & Dünnhaupt Verlag (6), 1935-1938 (Box-folder 20: 20)
  - Kafka, Gustav E. (6), 1960-1961 (Box-folder 20: 21)
    Includes correspondence with Ernst Fraenkel, Heinz Laufer, Franz-Martin Schmölz
  - Kahler, Erich (2), 1930 (Box-folder 20: 22)
  - Kaiser, Joseph H. (3), 1950 (Box-folder 20: 23)
  - Kallir, Moina M. (3), 1942 (Box-folder 20: 24)
  - Kallmann, Hans (3), 1944 (Box-folder 20: 25)
  - Kämpf, Helmut (9), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 20: 26)
  - Kappelmacher, Hans (1), 1939 (Box-folder 20: 27)
  - Kariel, Henry S. (2), 1974 (Box-folder 20: 28)
  - Kaspar, Leo (2), 1938 (Box-folder 20: 29)
    Includes correspondence with the Society of Friends. Germany Emergency Committee
  - Kästner, Wolfgang (2), 1984 (Box-folder 20: 30)
  - Katholische Akademie in Bayern (Karl Forster) (10), 1961-1963 (Box-folder 20: 31)
  - Kauder, Emil L. (23), 1939-1951 (Box-folder 20: 32)
  - Kauffungen, Kunz von (2), 1967 (Box-folder 20: 33)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (11), 1939-1946 (Box-folder 20: 34)
  - Kaufmann, Fritz (6), 1939-1945 (Box-folder 20: 35)
  - Kellerer, Hans (1), 1962 (Box-folder 20: 36)
  - Kelsen, Hans (5), 1939-1954 (Box-folder 20: 37)
  - Kendall, Nellie (4), 1973 (Box-folder 20: 38)
  - Kendall, Willmoore (35), 1941-1966 (Box-folder 20: 39)
  - Kessler, Emil and Pia (6), 1962-1981 (Box-folder 20: 40)
  - Keulman, Kenneth (6), 1978-1981 (Box-folder 21: 1)
  - Kim, Dae Jung (1), 1983 (Box-folder 21: 2)
  - Kim, Taekhoan (4), 1970-1979 (Box-folder 21: 3)
  - King, Winston L. (2), 1964 (Box-folder 21: 4)
  - Kirby, John S. (3), 1974 (Box-folder 21: 5)
  - Kirk, Russell (15), 1956-1971 (Box-folder 21: 6)
  - Kissinger, Henry A. (41), 1958-1961 (Box-folder 21: 7)
  - Klett-Cotta (4), 1956-1980 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Klinghoffer, Hans (6), 1938-1948 (Box-folder 21: 9)
    Includes correspondence with the Society for the Protection of Science and Learning, and the National Refugee Service. See also Erich Hula
  - Knöpfle, F. (1), 1974 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Knox, T. M. (1), 1966 (Box-folder 21: 11)
    See also Helmut Kuhn
  - Koch, Hans (5), 1958 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Koch, Hede and Karl (64), 1947-1957 (Box-folder 21: 13)
    Cousin of Eric Voegelin
  - Koch, Peter (30), 1948-1979 (Box-folder 21: 14)
    Cousin once removed of Eric Voegelin (son of Hede and Karl Koch)
  - König, Marie E. P. (76), 1968-1984 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Korsch, Karl (4), 1945 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Kösel-Verlag (Heinrich Wild) (76), 1955-1973 (Box-folder 22: 1)
    Includes correspondence with Rusconi Editore
  - Köstler, Josef Nikolaus (4), 1960-1961 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Kotter, Ludwig (1), 1966 (Box-folder 22: 3)
  - Kramm, Lothar (15), 1979-1984 (Box-folder 22: 4)
  - Kratochwil, Friedrich Viktor (4), 1969-1984 (Box-folder 22: 5)
  - Krausnick, Helmut (5), 1960-1968 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Kriele, Martin (2), 1968 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Krings, Hermann (2), 1966 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Krumholz, Walter. See Freie Universität Berlin, Otto-Suhr-Institut
  - Kuczynski, Jürgen (4), 1966 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik Ritter and Christiane von (5), 1966-1970 (Box-folder 22: 10)
  - Kuhn, Helmut (15), 1952-1981 (Box-folder 22: 11)
  - Küng, Hans (3), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 22: 12)
  - Kunkel, Charles Fr. (2), 1967 (Box-folder 22: 13)
  - Kunkel, Wolfgang (1), 1960 (Box-folder 22: 14)
  - Kuntz, Paul G. (Grinnell College) (20), 1962-1979 (Box-folder 22: 15)
    Includes correspondence with Paul M. Downing
  - Kunz, Joseph L. (4), 1944-1950 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - Kütemeyer, Wilhelm (6), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Ladner, Gerhart (1), 1965 (Box-folder 22: 18)
  - Lami, Gian Franco (3), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22: 19)
  - Landess, Thomas H. (4), 1970 (Box-folder 22: 20)
  - Lane, Frederic C. (2), 1949 (Box-folder 22: 21)
  - Langan, Thomas (3), 1978-1982 (Box-folder 22: 22)
  - Langlois, Jean (2), 1964 (Box-folder 22: 23)
  - Larsen, J. (2), 1951 (Box-folder 22: 24)
  - Lasky, Melvin J. (3), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 22: 25)
  - Laslett, Peter (4), 1973 (Box-folder 22: 26)
  - Laufer, Heinz (22), 1961-1983 (Box-folder 22: 27)
    See also Gustav E. Kafka
  - Lawrence, Frederick (Boston College) (1), 1982 (Box-folder 22: 28)
  - Lawson, Ruth C. (3), 1968 (Box-folder 22: 29)
  - Leclerc, Ivor (5), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22: 30)
  - Legaz y Lacambra, Luis (1), 1962 (Box-folder 22: 31)
  - Lehner, Frederick (2), 1939 (Box-folder 22: 32)
  - Lehrl, Joseph (6), 1948-1949 (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - Leisner, Walter (1), 1962 (Box-folder 23: 2)
  - Lemche, Ruthilt and Karsten (9), 1938-1946 (Box-folder 23: 3)
  - Lepenies, Wolf (1), 1975 (Box-folder 23: 4)
  - Leuschner, Peter (17), 1965-1975 (Box-folder 23: 5)
  - Levant, Howard (1), 1975 (Box-folder 23: 6)
  - Levenson, Joseph R. (3), 1959 (Box-folder 23: 7)
  - Levi, Werner (32), 1965-1971 (Box-folder 23: 8)
    See also Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange between East and West
  - Levy, David J. (7), 1979-1984 (Box-folder 23: 9)
  - Lewis, John D. (4), 1957-1959 (Box-folder 23: 10)
  - Lewy, Guenther (5), 1961-1969 (Box-folder 23: 11)
  - Lieser, Lene (1), 1940 (Box-folder 23: 12)
  - Lilienthal, Robinson (1), 1975 (Box-folder 23: 13)
  - Linebarger, Paul (4), 1960 (Box-folder 23: 14)
  - Lippincott, Benjamin E. (University of Minnesota) (8), 1940-1979 (Box-folder 23: 15)
  - Lippucci, Alessandra and David Edwards (8), 1975-1980 (Box-folder 23: 16)